[Music]
hello everyone I had enormous plans this
week of a lot of projects I wanted to
get done and I started all of them and I
finished none of them I ended up picking
up a bug from my job I work at a
bookstore I do retail so um I think I
picked up something from doing the
holiday season when everything is kind
of so stuffy indoors I'm on the mend and
very excited to finally finish some of
these projects finally get all the
things done that I've been wanting to
get done I've been trying to reopen my
Etsy Shop what feels like forever this
month so next week will be the week it
will happen I know it with all that
being said I just wanted to share with
you something this week that was very
exciting to me I know it is not relevant
to everyone and I know not everyone's
interested but it is something really
big for me and a big part of my life and
so I did want to very briefly share that
Luke and I just found out that we were
having a baby boy we didn't have a
preference but finding out was such a
big deal for us more than I thought it
would be because suddenly I am starting
to visualize a little bit of what our
family might be looking like by the
summer and it's just been really
interesting and wonderful fascinating
experience so far the topic for next
week's video is one that I just wanted
to tell you really quick to see if it's
something that resonates with any of you
and it is something that I realize that
I really need to work on this year
throughout my life I have struggled with
self-trust and self-confidence but it
manifests in me a little bit different
from maybe The Stereotype I am confident
in many aspects of my life obvious
viously I enjoy creating videos and
putting them out there and um that is
something really wonderful and
beneficial for me that is help me come
out of my shell even more however I do
notice when it comes to making decisions
about my life and making choices I
really like when other people make those
decisions for me and there's nothing
wrong with bringing in input from other
people but I'm realizing now that I
sometimes go to other people's opinions
and choices so much that I don't really
trust my own ability to make good
choices and I don't even always trust in
my own ability to think through things
and I assume that there are many people
that can relate to this maybe some
people not but definitely share down
below if you have had experience with
this or you have some advice it is
something I'm going to dive into next
week but I just wanted to share it
because it's something I'm realizing
2024 kind of needs to be all about if if
you're looking to develop more
assuredness in yourself more trust and
belief that you can do things that you
are stronger than you think that you are
capable of making good choices so yes
that is something that I'm working on in
my personal life right now and it's
something I'm going to talk about next
week I talked about it a bit on patreon
and that's when I realized that um there
were a few people at least that really
relate to this I wanted to dive in more
to hopefully encourage myself and Hope
hopefully connect with all of you I know
I don't need to apologize for not having
a video up but I really wanted to have
one up this week that's all I'm going to
say today but thank you again for being
here we will see you very soon sending
so much love
[Music]
goodbye